A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Japanese Studies and Korean Studies, Record Group 3, Series 7 FA1775
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) program files, 1945-1995; 2; 5.77 Cubic Feet 15 document boxes: 14.25 letter size boxes and .75 legal size box
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars Asia Program - Wild Asters: Explorations in Korean Thought, Culture, and Society, undated (Box 51, Folder 589)
  - Dankook University Institute of Oriental Studies - The Oriental Studies Vol. 18, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 590)
  - Dankook University Institute of Oriental Studies publication, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 591)
  - Korean Social Science Journal Vol. XII, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 592)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1988 Meeting, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 593)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1987 Meeting (Box 51, Folder 594)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1987 Meeting (Box 51, Folder 595)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) general file, 1985-1987 (Box 51, Folder 596)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) role in Korean Studies field - Funding initiatives, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 597)
  - SSRC Africa Program Research Training Fellowship 1987-1988 application packets, circa 1987 (Box 51, Folder 598)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1987 Meeting - Tentative agenda, 1986-1987 (Box 52, Folder 599)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1988 Meeting - Tentative agenda, 1987-1988 (Box 52, Folder 600)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1988 Meeting - Tentative agenda (Box 52, Folder 601)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant and Dissertation Fellowship 1988-1989 awards lists, circa 1988 (Box 52, Folder 602)
  - Political economy of Korea, Stephan Haggard - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 603)
  - Political economy of Korea, Stephan Haggard, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 604)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) North Korea initiative, 1986-1988 (Box 52, Folder 605)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) North Korea scholarly exchange - Gari Keith Ledyard aborted trip, 1979-1986 (Box 52, Folder 606)
  - Korean Research Foundation (KRF) - Korean Studies Program guide, undated (Box 52, Folder 607)
  - SSRC International Doctoral Research Fellowship Program 1989 Information Book, circa 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 608)
- Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) grant and fellowship awardees, 1984-1990; 3; 1.26 Cubic Feet 3.25 document boxes: 3 letter size boxes and .25 legal size boxes
  Files in the subseries document awardees of the Social Science Research Council's (SSRC) Joint Committee on Japanese Studies' (JCJS) different grant and fellowship programs. As the contents of the subseries demonstrates, the subseries does not hold the files for all awardees of these programs. The award years documented within the subseries span from the mid-1980s to 1990. The grant and fellowship programs the JCJS administered which the subseries documents include:
  - Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship for pre-doctoral researchers - Advanced Research Grant for post-doctoral researchers
  Awardee files include the applicant's research proposal and accompanying application materials as well as the award letter and other evidence of the awardee's grant or fellowship such as reports and correspondence.
  Awardees documented within the subseries researched such subject areas as religion, economics, economic development, trade relations, anthropology, history, sociology, culture, literature, gender, women, and linguistics in relation to Japan.
  Awardee grant and fellowship files are arranged chronologically by the award program year, and within those chronological groupings, the files have been arranged according to what award program they pertain.
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1986-1987 awardees - Vaida, Nancy, 1985-1988 (Box 52, Folder 609)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1987-1988 awardees - Doak, Kevin, 1986-1989 (Box 53, Folder 610-611)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1987-1988 awardees - Culter, Suzanne, 1986-1989 (Box 53, Folder 612)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Vogel, David J., 1986-1989 (Box 53, Folder 613)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Dobbins, James C., 1986-1988 (Box 53, Folder 614)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Flanagan, Scott C., 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 615)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Hardacre, Helen, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 616)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Ito, Ken, 1986-1988 (Box 53, Folder 617)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Kramer, Robert W., 1986-1988 (Box 53, Folder 618)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Maraldo, John C., 1986-1988 (Box 53, Folder 619)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - MacDougal, Terry E., 1984-1987 (Box 53, Folder 620)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Reich, Michael, 1986-1989 (Box 53, Folder 621)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Edwards, Walter, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 622)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Robertson, Jennifer, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 623)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Sheiner, Irwin, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 624)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Smith, Thomas, 1986-1988 (Box 54, Folder 625)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - Tamanoi, Mariko, 1986-1988 (Box 54, Folder 626)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 awardees - White, Merry I., 1986-1989 (Box 54, Folder 627)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1988-1989 awardees - Mazuka, Reiko, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 628)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1988-1989 awardees - Milly, Deborah, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 629)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1988-1989 awardees - Tilton, Mark, 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 630)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1988-1989 awardees - Wigen, Karen, 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 631)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Bestor, Ted, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 632)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Bognar, Botund, 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 633)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Field, Rodger, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 634)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Finlayson, Grant, 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 635)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Flath, David, 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 636)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Garon, Sheldon, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 637)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Lebra, Takie, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 638)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Maynard, Senko Kumiya, 1987-1990 (Box 55, Folder 639)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Fong, Glenn, 1987-1989 (Box 55, Folder 640)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Miyoshi, Masao, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 641)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Molony, Barbara, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 642)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Peak, Lois, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 643)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 awardees - Rubinger, Richard, 1987-1989 (Box 55, Folder 644)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 awardees - Miyake, Yoshiko, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 645)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 awardees - Pratt, Edward, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 646)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 awardees - Ragsdale, Kathryn, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 647)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 awardees - Uriu, Robert, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 648)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 awardees - Adams, Robert, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 649)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 awardees - Keyser, Donna, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 650)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 awardees - Jones, Kimberly, 1987-1989 (Box 55, Folder 651)
- Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) grant and fellowship declinations and withdrawals, 1968-1996; 4; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 document boxes: 9 letter size boxes
  Files in this subseries document applicants to the Social Science Research Council's (SSRC) Joint Committee on Japanese Studies' (JCJS) different grant and fellowship programs who did not get an award. Most of the applicants were declined acceptance by the JCJS, some were initially designated as alternates but were then declined, and some were awarded a grant or fellowship but then withdrew, mostly because they received grant support from other sources. As the contents of the subseries demonstrates, the subseries does not hold the files for all declinations of these programs. The award years documented within the subseries originate from the early 1970s and then span from the mid 1980s to the end of JCJS in 1996 with some gaps within that time span. The grant and fellowship programs the JCJS administered which the subseries documents include:
  - Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship for pre-doctoral researchers
  - Advanced Research Grant for post-doctoral researchers
  - Research Planning Grant
  - Dissertation Workshop
  Files include the applicant's research proposal and accompanying application materials as well as the declination letter from the JCJS. Some files include other documents like additional correspondence.
  Applicants documented within the subseries sought to research such subject areas as economics, international trade, economic development, labor, industry, religion, Buddhism, culture, art, literature, film, linguistics, law, politics, nationalism, international relations, history, anthropology, gender, women, education, child development, family studies, sociology, psychology, criminology, sexuality, and technology in relation to Japan.
  Files are arranged chronologically by the award program year, and within those chronological groupings, the files have been arranged according to what award program they pertain.
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Grant 1972-1974 declinations, 1968-1973 (Box 64, Folder 652)
    Restricted confidential material
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1984-1985 declinations - Unger, James, 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 653)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1984-1985 declinations - Valsiner, Jaan, 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 654)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1984-1985 declinations - Vlam, Grace, 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 655)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1984-1985 declinations - Vining, Daniel R., 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 656)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1984-1985 declinations - Wilson, George, 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 657)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Karjala, Yoko, 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 658)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Kikuoka, Michael, 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 659)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Kunkel, Peter H., 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 660)
    This applicant was reviewed by both the Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) and Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS).
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Koshal, Munjulika, 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 661)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Hasegawa, Nobuko, 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 662)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Hill, Anne M., 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 663)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Holmes, Ann, 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 664)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1985-1986 declinations - Hodder, James, 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 665)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1986-1987 declinations - Chung, Jun Ki, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 666)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1986-1987 declinations - Rhee, Margie, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 667)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Tsurutani, Taketsugu, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 668)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 withdrawals - Upham, Frank K., 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 669)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Webb, Robert, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 670)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Zimmerman, Edyth J., 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 671)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Late applications, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 672)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Judge Thornton, Robert, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 673)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Treat, John, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 674)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Traweek, Sharon, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 675)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Picone, Mary J., 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 676)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 withdrawals - Ramirez-Christensen, E., 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 677)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 withdrawals - Robertson, Jennifer, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 678)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Santa-Pinter, Jose Julio, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 679)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Smith, Bardwell L., 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 680)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Kilson, Marion, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 681)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Kuroda, Yasumasa, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 682)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Lee, Chung-Myun and Kontuly, Robert, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 683)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 withdrawals - Lyons, Phyllis I., 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 684)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Napier, Susan J., 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 685)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 withdrawals - Graham, Patricia J., 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 686)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Harrison, Lucia Anne, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 687)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Hinds, Wako Tawa, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 688)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Bell, David C., 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 689)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Akiyama, M. Michael, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 690)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Duus, Masayo, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 691)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Darling, Bruce L., 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 692)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Cooke, Gerald, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 693)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Gumpert, Gary and Cathcart, Robert, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 694)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Ito, Takatoshi, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 695)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Hirai, Atsuko, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 696)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Bess, James, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 697)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Birt, Michael, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 698)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Boyd, Carl, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 699)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - King, Mary L., 1985-1987 (Box 57, Folder 700)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - McDonald, Keiko I., 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 701)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Mourdoukoutas, Panos, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 702)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Murakami, Paul K., 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 703)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Nanto, Dick, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 704)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Napier, Susan, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 705)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Shwalb, David and Barbara, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 706)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Whitman, Nancy, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 707)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 withdrawals - Allison, Anne, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 708)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 withdrawals - Kiley, Cornelius, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 709)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 withdrawals - Mochizuki, Mike M., 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 710)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 withdrawals - Viswanathan, Meera S., 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 711)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 withdrawals - Lyons, Phyllis I., 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 712)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Akiyama, M. Michael, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 713)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - McCreary, Don, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 714)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Fang, Irving, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 715)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Butow, R.J.C., 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 716)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Brinton, Mary, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 717)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1988-1989 declinations - Beechler, Schon, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 718)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Fukushima, Kaz, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 719)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Kim, Manjae, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 720)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Kusakabe, Yuko, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 721)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Kim, Kunae, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 722)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Lipson, James, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 723)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Lipson, Kyoko, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 724)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Miller, Ronald, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 725)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Morimoto, Toyotomi, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 726)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Palugod, Nora, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 727)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Thakur, Yoko, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 728)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Rhine, Marjorie, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 729)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Rickman, Barney, 1985-1989 (Box 59, Folder 730)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Schneider, Michael, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 731)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Dissertation Write-Up Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Takao, Yasuo, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 732)